So it's come to my attention that I'm not just being shadow banned.
I think I'm specifically being shadow banned from my Black audience.
Which means we are going to have to go back to the grassroots.
And I'm asking y'all, the Black folks who are not shadow banned from my page,
to be the mouthpieces to spread the word when I have a post that you like,
when I'm going to be doing a show in your town,
when I'm doing something online,
whether it's the Common Sense Kickback or Small Doses podcast.
You know, I'm asking, like genuinely asking,
that you all share that stuff in your group chats,
when you're on the phone, at your brunches,
at your lunches, with your sorors, with your frat, etc.
Because Meta is definitely...